{
    "id": "a373078de2e8490bb8df7b55978b92d6",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have invited them ………………………….. lunch.",
            "description": "You invite people to an event. ",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You are not supposed to park …………………………… double yellow lanes.",
            "description": "Use on to indicate position on the surface. ",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She took some money ………………………….. her wallet.",
            "description": "Out of is the opposite of into.",
            "answers": [
                "out of",
                "out",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The people in my office are all easy to get ………………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "by with",
                "on",
                "on with",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Take that stupid smile ……………………………. your face.",
            "description": "To take something off is to remove it. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "off",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There were remains of the meal all ………………………….. the floor.",
            "description": "All over means everywhere. ",
            "answers": [
                "across",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The road goes …………………………….. a steep hill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You know that girl …………………………. a brother who plays the piano?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I am quite pleased …………………………….. myself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "by",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She suffers …………………………….. an incurable disease.",
            "description": "People suffer from illnesses. ",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "What is wrong ……………………………… you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Why are you always yelling ……………………………… me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "at",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}